[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Douglas：这是我们浏览器的流程图。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: So this is a flow chart of our browser.
这就是最初的Web浏览器的工作方式。
This is how the original web browser worked.
你可以把它想象成一条蛇。
You can think of it as a snake.
你把你的网址放在一边，把像素放在另一边。
You put your URL's on one side, your get pixels out the other side.
因此，您将URL提供给它，该URL进入获取引擎，然后获取引擎将出去
So you feed it with the URL that goes to the fetch engine which will then go out on
在互联网上找到东西并把它带回来，并把它放在缓存中。
the Internet and find the thing and bring it back, and put it in the cache.
然后将其提供给解析引擎，解析引擎将对其进行解析并将其转换为
Then it gets given to the parse engine which will parse it and turn it into
树，树是表示文档的数据结构。
a tree, the tree being the data structure which represents the document.
然后将树提供给流或布局引擎，后者将计算出
The tree is then given to the flow or layout engine which will figure out
页面的所有组件，它们有多大，以及
all of the components of the page,how big they are and
它们是如何彼此相对定位并创建显示列表的。
how they're all located relative to each other and create a display list.
然后将显示列表提供给绘制引擎，然后由绘制引擎将其旋转
And then the display list gets given to the paint engine which will then turn it
所有这些都变成像素，然后您可以将其发送到屏幕或打印机。
all into pixels which you can then send to the screen or to the printer.
所有的浏览器基本上都是这样做的。
All browsers still do essentially that.
当马赛克浏览器开始工作时，他们添加了图像标签。
When work started on the Mosaic browser, they added the image tag.
这就是他们想出的让图像标签工作的方法。
So this is the hack that they came up with for making the image tag work.
当他们到达解析引擎时，他们会得到一个图像标签，
When they got to the parse engine and they'd get an image tag,
他们会停下来，偷偷地回到取回引擎，说去拿那张照片，然后
they'd stop, sneak back to the fetch engine, say go get that picture and
他们会等待它回来，然后继续解析。
they'd wait for it to come back and then they'd resume parsing.
他们在世界上最快的大学网络之一，所以
They were on one of the world's fastest university networks, so
这对他们来说真的很管用。
that was working really well for them.
但是，马赛克松开了，进入了这个世界
But, Mosaic got loose, got into the world and
当时我们还在使用拨号调制解调器。
at that time we were still on dial up modems.
任何人都记得拨号调制解调器，任何人都可以唱拨号调制解调器的歌曲。
Anybody remember dial up modems, can anybody sing the dial up modem song.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：[笑]&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：是的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [LAUGH] &gt;&gt; Douglas: Yeah.
是啊。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：叮，叮。
Yeah. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Ding, ding, ding.
&gt；&gt；Douglas：因此在这些调制解调器上运行Mosaic的经验是
&gt;&gt; Douglas: And so the experience of running Mosaic on those modems was that
您将等待，直到每个图像都被加载，然后一切都会显示出来。
you would wait until every image got loaded and then everything would display.
因此，可能需要很长时间才能使网页正常运行。
So it could take a long time to get a web page going.
于是，这些孩子们搬到了网景公司，他们的目标是杀死马赛克。
So those kids then moved to Netscape, and their goal is to kill Mosaic.
他们想创造一个杀死马赛克的怪物，所以他们制作了一个Mozilla。
They want to create a monster that kills Mosaic, so they make a Mozilla.
Mozilla的工作方式略有不同。
And Mozilla works a little differently.
因此，当解析引擎到达图像标记时，它将转到提取引擎并
So when the parse engine gets to an image tag, it goes to the fetch engine and
说Go get it，但它们随后继续解析。
says go get it but they then resume parsing.
他们在树中放置了一个占位符来表示图片
They put a placeholder in the tree to represent the picture and
它们继续解析。
they continue to parse.
如果他们看到另一个图像标记，他们告诉提取引擎也得到一个
And if they see another image tag, they tell the fetch engine get that one too and
在树中放入第二个占位符，它们将继续解析。
put a second placeholder in the tree and they continue parsing.
然后在最后，他们会展示他们到目前为止所取得的成果。
And then at the end, they will display what they've got so far.
所以你会看到这个东西中的小占位符，但是你马上就看到了文本。
And so you would see little placeholders in the thing but you saw text right away.
然后当取数引擎递送图像时，
And then as the fetch engine delivers the images,
然后，他们重复流程和油漆，以纳入新的东西。
they then repeat the flow and the paint to incorporate the new things.
所以在它去的地方会有一个动画效果，砰，
And so there'd be an animation effect where it go, boom, boom, boom, boom,
正如图像所显示的那样。
as the images would appear.
所以总的来说，这可能比在马赛克上花费的时间更长，但是
So overall this could take longer than it did on Mosaic, but
用户体验要好得多，因为他们可以立即看到东西。
the user experience was much better because they would see things immediately.
所以它很受欢迎，
And so it was a hit,
它非常成功，今天所有的浏览器基本上都在这样做。
it was very successful, and all browsers today are essentially doing that.
只是网络正在变得如此
It's just that networks are going so
快到我们再也看不到占位符了。
fast that we don't see the placeholders anymore.
因此，在Netscape Navigator 2中，他们添加了脚本。
So in Netscape Navigator 2, they added scripting.
所以现在浏览器中有一个事件循环，看起来像这样。
So there's now an event loop in the browser which looks something like this.
我们会做布局，我们会画。
We'll do the layout, we'll do the painting.
然后我们将等待可能发生的事件
We'll then wait for an event which could be something happening with
当有人移动鼠标或在键盘上键入时的UI。
the UI if someone moving a mouse or typing on a keyboard.
或者可能是从取数引擎传来的东西，
Or it could be something coming from the fetch engine,
网络上发生了一些事情。
something happened on the network.
或者它可以是一个计时器提示，表示已经过去了一些时间，并且发生了一些事情。
Or it could be a timer cue saying some time has elapsed and something happens.
无论它是什么，它都会导致一些脚本运行。
Whatever it is, it will cause some script to run.
并且该脚本将运行到完成。
And that script will run to completion.
它保证它不会被下一个事件打断，这是一件好事。
It's guaranteed it will not be interrupted by the next event which is a good thing.
因为它使脚本更容易编写。
Cuz it makes the the scripts much easier to write.
该脚本可能会以某种方式变异树，
That script will probably mutate the tree in some way,
这些事件可能导致想要展示的东西或
that the events probably caused something to want to be displayed or
修改，这意味着我们将做另一个流程和其他油漆
modified, which means we'll then do another flow and other paint and
然后我们将获得下一个事件，以此类推，这基本上就是浏览器所做的。
then we'll get the next event and so on, and that's basically what browsers do.
现在，这是一个非常简单的方法。
Now this is way over simplified.
树的一些突变将导致流立即发生。
There are some mutations of the tree which will cause flow to happen immediately.
所以不一定是在这些非常干净的阶段，
So it's not in these very clean phases necessarily,
但这几乎就是他们的工作方式。
but this is pretty much how they work.
这是浏览器的方式。
This is the way of the browser.
他们都这么做。
They all do that.